https://www.coolworks.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy PolicyDry Tortugas National Park, FloridaWe respect your privacy. In these days of spam and online scams, we at Cool Works® are sensitive to the issues of protecting your privacy and your identity. We try to provide the safest possible environment for you to search and apply for jobs. next-section ?> Home » Privacy PolicyPERSONAL INFORMATIONCool Works® collects personal information from users on a voluntary basis only. This allows us to give you private and secure areas for job seekers and employers to post and edit content on our site. We do not sell your personal information to anyone for any reason. When you voluntarily distribute or display personal information such as your email address or resume, others may be able to collect and use it. As a result, you may receive unsolicited messages from third parties for which Cool Works® is not responsible.Our sites contain links to other Web sites over which we have no control. Cool Works® is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of other Web sites to which you choose to link from Cool Works®. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of those other Web sites so you can understand how they collect, use and share your information.Please remember that if you post any of your personal information in public areas of Cool Works®, such as in online forums or chat rooms, such information may be collected and used by others over whom Cool Works® has no control. We are not responsible for the use made by third parties of information you post or otherwise make available in public areas of Cool Works®.We use the information we gather, whether personal, demographic, collective or technical, for the purpose of operating and improving Cool Works®, fostering a positive user experience, and delivering the products and services that we offer. We may also use the information we gather to inform you of other products or services available from Cool Works® or to contact you about your opinion regarding potential new products and services that may be offered. We may use your contact information in order to send you e-mail or other communications regarding updates at Cool Works®. We have an area where you may submit feedback. Any feedback you submit becomes our property, and we can use such feedback (such as success stories) for marketing purposes or contact you for further information.We may also use or disclose information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to applicable law or comply with legal process served on us or the Site; (b) protect and defend the our rights or property, the Site or our users, and (c) act under emergency circumstances to protect the personal safety of us, our affiliates, agents, or the users of the Site or the public.This Site is not directed towards children under the age of 13, and we request that children under 13 not use this Site without prior parental consent.  We also request that children under the age of 13 not provide personally identifiable information to the Site.ABOUT COOKIESWe use cookies at Cool Works® only for the protection and convenience of our users. Cookies enable us to serve secure pages to our users without asking them to sign in repeatedly. If a user’s system is idle for more than an hour, however, the cookie will expire, forcing the user to sign in again to continue their session. This prevents unauthorized access to the user’s information while they are away from their computer.JOB POSTER’S RULESYou may not:impersonate another person, living or dead;post false, inaccurate or misleading information;post advertisements or solicitations of businesspost chain letters or pyramid schemes; orpost opinions or notices, commercial or otherwise.JOB SEEKER RULESCool Works® is under no obligation to monitor the conduct of its Users, but it may investigate and respond when violations are reported. You may not:impersonate another person, living or dead;post false, inaccurate or misleading information;post advertisements or solicitations of businesspost chain letters or pyramid schemes; orpost opinions or notices, commercial or otherwise.Cool Works® makes no representations or guarantees regarding the truthfulness, accuracy, completeness, timeliness or reliability of any information posted by Users, or of any other form of communication engaged in by Users.YOU ASSUME ALL RESPONSIBILITY AND RISK FOR YOUR USE OF THE SITE, THE INTERNET GENERALLY, AND THE INFORMATION YOU POST OR ACCESS AND FOR YOUR CONDUCT ON AND OFF THE SITE.SOME IMPORTANT TIPS TO USE WHEN DEALING WITH PROSPECTIVE EMPLOYERSDo not give out your social security number.Never provide credit card or bank numbers on an employment application.Be cautious when dealing with contacts from other countries.Do not provide any non-work related personal information (i.e. social security number, eye color, marital status etc.) over the phone or online.OTHER PRIVACY FEATURES ON COOL WORKSYou never need to provide data to search for jobs.Choice/Opt-Out. Cool Works® provides you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving most communications from Cool Works®. You have the option to remove your information from our database and to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. We also give you the option to change or modify the information previously provided. To exercise any of these options:Contact us with the details of your requestSend a letter to PO Box 383, Morrison, CO 80465Call us at (406) 848-2380* * * * * * * * * * *Note that, by using Cool Works® Services, you signify your agreement to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Policy, please do not use the Services. Your continued use of the Services subsequent to changes to this Policy will mean that you accept the changes. eNEWSLETTER SIGNUPGet the latest job postings, news and updates, job seeker tips and inspiration, CoolWorks contest info, and more - right to your inbox!
bg bgAbout CoolWorksSince 1995, CoolWorks has been a leader in connecting people seeking meaningful and exciting work with the employers who are looking for their enthusiasm, energy, and knowledge. We believe that you can and should love your life, and we want to help make that happen! We feature job opportunities in great places — from national parks to ski resorts, dude ranches to summer camps, and everything in between.LEARN MORE.Contact CoolWorksHave a question about a job or a place? Need a little extra encouragement? Know of a great place that we haven’t discovered yet? Send us an email, tag us with #CoolWorksJobs on Social, or release the courier pigeons. Contact us. We would love to hear from you!Get Connectedmycwfacebooktwitterinstagram Let's get social! Follow CoolWorks, share your experiences, and stay connected!Join the community that’s dedicated to jobs in great places. FIND A JOB POST A JOB
